WARNING! The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
Mr. Hennie Ferreira has come to The SCOAN, seeking the face of God for divine healing
from the terrible problem of leg cancer.
Imagine the excruciating pain and social embarrassment
this leg cancer would cause him on a daily basis.
The flesh is rotting and completely exposed.
A closer look reveals two large open wounds on his legs,
where the infected skin has been eaten away.
But he has come, believing that his problem does not embarrass Jesus Christ
because He has a solution.
My name is Hennie Ferreira. I am 42 years old.
What is the problem that brought you here to The SCOAN?
Leg cancer.
How long have you had this problem?
I have had this problem for approximately one year now.
I have got a lot of pains and I have had a lot of operations
but the treatment from the doctors hasn't relieved me of the pain.
I believe that God Almighty will heal me when the Prophet prays for me.
Now seated at the prayer line of The SCOAN,
Mr Hennie Ferreira waits in faith for a healing touch from Jesus Christ
through the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, be healed!
A spiritual operation is taking place,
as the healing power of Jesus Christ is released into his system.
The sickness in the life of Mr Ferreira is going out
because it has been commanded to go in Jesus' name.
Jesus Christ purchased our complete healing at the price of great suffering.
For by His wounds, we are healed.
Jesus, the great Restorer, is restoring Mr Ferreira
to the original position in which he was created in perfect health.
You are free.
Hallelujah! He has been declared free in Jesus' name.
After his healing, Mr. Ferreira returned to his country of South Africa.
Now, he has come back after one year
to testify to his perfect and complete healing in Jesus' name.
Let's listen to him.
TESTIMONY TIME
Before and After
Yeah!
I am healed!
I am saved!
The smile on Mr. Ferreira's face is one of joy and gratitude to God.
"Thank you" is a response from a happy heart.
He happily shows the skin on his legs, where the terrible cancer once was.
Now, the skin is smooth and the wound has completely healed.
A steadfast look at the crucified one never looks in vein at the great physician.
Jesus Christ is the great physician.
When He heals, He heals effectually, He heals completely.
Thank You, Jesus.
Let's listen to his testimony.
I'm redeemed!
I'm born again!
Hallelujah!
Praise the Lord!
My name is Hennie Ferreira.
I'm here to testify about the healing that I received at The SCOAN.
A year ago, I was here for healing of leg cancer.
The night the Prophet prayed for me, I knew I was completely healed.
Today I am here to testify.
Actually, there was nothing the doctors could do for me or the pain.
Since that night, I have not used any injection.
My pain is gone.
I'm so glad that God healed me of leg cancer.
Here, you can all see what happened.
The other side - there is also no pain.
Testimony Time
My promise to God is that I will sin no more and I will always serve God.
Praise God!
This is the leg. You can see I have no more pain.
My leg is completely healed.
Thank God for that.
The second one also.
Mr. Ferreira demonstrates how he can now touch the place
where the cancer once was on his legs.
His pain is a thing of the past.
His testimony has truly been restored.
Glory be to God!
RV: Mel Flowers 25/03/2019